magicpin.in 2019-04-12

# magicpin Privacy Policy

This privacy policy governs your use of the software application magicpin for mobile devices that was created by Samast Technologies(“Application”). The Application is meant for finding interesting deals and discounts around your location.

## What information does the Application obtain and how is it used?

### User Provided Information

The Application obtains the information you provide when you download and register the Application.

When you register with us and use the Application, you generally provide (a) your name, email address, phone number and other registration information; (b) transaction-related information, such as when you make purchases, upload a selfie, respond to any offers, or download or use any applications from us1; (c) information you provide us when you contact us for help; (d) any other information you enter into our system when using the Application, such as contact information and project management information.

### Automatically Collected Information

In addition, the Application may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile devices unique device ID, circle of the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the Application.

### Our Use of Your Information

We may use the information you provided us to contact you from time to time to provide you with important information, required notices and marketing promotions, [to improve our services and user experience on the Application, to enforce our legal rights as permitted under law, and otherwise with your consent.

## Does the Application collect precise real time location information of the device?

When you visit the mobile application, we may use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location in order to determine the city you are located within and display a location map with relevant advertisements. We will not share your current location with other users or partners.

## Do third parties see and/or have access to information obtained by the Application?

Yes. We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information:

We will NOT share your contact information at any point without your prior content, but your selfies, comments and other actions specific to our system might be visible to other users and merchants on the platform. However, without your prior consent such users will not have access to your contact information. You have the ability to remove your information from the system;  
As required by law, such as to comply with a summons, or similar legal process;  
When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request; With our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement [and apply data protection measures, at least equal to those set out below in the section “Data Security Measures”]. If Samast Technologies is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information. [We also may share data that is not linkable to a particular consumer or device (for example, information that has been aggregated with other records) for general business purposes.]

## What are my opt-out rights?

You can stop all collection of information by the Application easily by uninstalling the Application. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network. You can also request to opt-out via email, at [care@magicpin.in](mailto:care@magicpin.in).

### Data Retention Policy, Managing Your Information

We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. We will retain Automatically Collected information for up to 24 months and thereafter may store it in aggregate. If youâ€™d like us to delete User Provided Data that you have provided via the Application, please contact us at [care@magicpin.in](mailto:care@magicpin.in) and we will respond in a reasonable time. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data may be required in order for the Application to function properly.

### Children

We do not use the Application to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [care@magicpin.in](mailto:care@magicpin.in). We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time2

### Data Security Measures

We have in place various procedures to safeguard your information, including technical, administrative and physical procedures intended to keep your information secure. In this regard we follow the measures set out under the International Standard IS/ISO/IEC 27001 on “Information Technology-Security Techniques – Information Security Management System – Requirements”. However, please note that no security system can prevent all potential security breaches. 

In addition, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Application. 

### Changes

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy here. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes. You can check the history of this policy by clicking here.

### Your Consent

By using the Application, you are consenting to our Processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing, means using cookies on a computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information.

### Contact us

If you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at [care@magicpin.in](mailto:care@magicpin.in).

### [ Your Privacy Is Our Priority ](https://magicpin.in/blog/understanding-consumer-privacy/)

* * *

1\. What about user reviews and any communication between users (if applicable?)

2\. Can you also say that it is our constant endeavour that only age appropriate content can be viewed by minors on the Application?
